<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jammed Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://jammedthoughts.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jammed Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jammedthoughts.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why read books when we forget?</title>
      <link>https://jammedthoughts.com/post/why_read_books_when_we_forget/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jammedthoughts.com/post/why_read_books_when_we_forget/</guid>
      <description>Reading is one of my favorite past times.
There was a point in time where I took the one book a week challenge where I tried to finish a non-fiction book every week. The idea that successful people read a lot was something I wanted to emulate. However, a few months in, I gave up.
I lost motivation, not because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t finish a book once a week. It&amp;rsquo;s because I forget most of what I read very quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratching My Own Itch</title>
      <link>https://jammedthoughts.com/post/scratching_my_own_itch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jammedthoughts.com/post/scratching_my_own_itch/</guid>
      <description>I love to learn. One of my favorite past time is challenging my preconceived notions. Being wrong for the right reasons puts me out of my comfort zone. Through it, I feel I am improving my life.
Yet, learning seems to be a frustrating and futile experience. Why frustrating and futile you ask? Because I tend to forget most of what I learned. After many rounds of this forgetting cycle, I have a sense that it is all for naught.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jammedthoughts.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jammedthoughts.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>